<resources>
    <string name="app_name"><b>Prabisha Startup Network</b></string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_activity">navigation_activity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="about_us_detail_first">They think and explore new ways to make our day to day life
        easier and better by implementing their billion dollar ideas on the ground.

Their ideas have the potential to change our world forever. Today, there are many examples
        like Oyo, Paytm, Google, Facebook, HP, Apple, Uber, Tesla, Yulu, etc. who started their journey as a
        startup and have changed our world forever from their unique offerings.

There are many more startup leaders who also have similar big ideas and are daring to change this world but
        COVID19 has impacted their life and work badly. These thought leaders need our help now much more than ever before.
    </string>
    <string name="about_us_detail_second">
        Prabisha Consulting, a trusted name in the area of Digital Marketing, Graphics
        Design and Technology Development is launching an initiative to help such start up leaders express their big
        ideas and share their dreams with all of us. We need to share their wonderful ideas and let them go far and wide
        to help the human kind get the best of these super leaders. We need to cut the clutter and provide them equitable opportunity
        and a promising platform for help, support and visibility.

Every week, promising Start up Leaders will share their thoughts, work, learnings and future plans on the platform of
        Prabisha Startup Network. Join us in this mission to help our thought leaders achieve their full potential.
    </string>
    <string name="PlanningOfStartup">How we are planning to create a startup ecosystem?</string>
    <string name="PSNMembership">PSN Membership</string>
    <string name="feed_information">Every week, promising Startup leaders will share their thoughts, work, learnings and future
        plans on our platform. This would
        be further amplified by PSN team on a number of online and offline platforms for greater visibility.</string>
    <string name="Home_heading">Who are startup leaders?</string>
    <string name="Home_information">Start Up leaders are real change makers of our times.
        They dare to dream.
        They think and explore new ways to make our day to day life easier and better by implementing their billion dollar ideas on the ground.
Their ideas have the potential to change our world forever. Today, there are many examples like Oyo,
        Paytm, Google, Facebook, HP, Apple, Uber, Tesla, Yulu, etc. who started their journey as a startup and have changed our world
        forever from their unique offerings.
There are many more startup leaders who also have similar big ideas and are daring to change this world but COVID19 has impacted their life and work badly.
        These thought leaders need our help now much more than ever before.</string>
    <string name="Who_we_are">Prabisha Startup Network is an initiative started by Prabisha Consulting,
        a trusted name in the area of Digital Marketing,Graphic Design and Technology Development.</string>
    <string name="Services_Branding_marketing">Branding and Marketing</string>
    <string name="Services_Website_Development">Website Design and Development</string>
    <string name="Services_Digital_Marketing">Digital Marketing</string>
    <string name="Services_Video_Animation_Prod">Video and Animation Production</string>
    <string name="Services_Company_Registration">Company Registration</string>
    <string name="Services_Hiring_Support">Hiring Support</string>
    <string name="Services_Website_Developmen_details"></string>
    <string name="Services_Digital_Marketing_deatils"></string>
    <string name="Services_Video_Animation_Prod_deatils"></string>
    <string name="Services_Branding_marketing_deatils"></string>

</resources>