<resources>
    <string name="app_name"><b>Prabisha Startup Network</b></string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="about_us_1">
<b>Start Up leaders are real change makers of our times. They dare to dream.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="about_us_2">
They think and explore new ways to make our day to day life easier and better by implementing their billion dollar ideas on the ground.

Their ideas have the potential to change our world forever. Today, there are many examples like Oyo, Paytm, Google, Facebook,
        HP, Apple, Uber, Tesla, Yulu, etc. who started their journey as a startup and have changed our world forever from their unique offerings.

There are many more startup leaders who also have similar big ideas and are daring to change this world but COVID19 has impacted
        their life and work badly. These thought leaders need our help now much more than ever before.


    </string>
    <string name="about_us_3">

        Prabisha Consulting, a trusted name in the area of Digital Marketing, Graphics Design and Technology Development is launching an
        initiative to help such start up leaders express their big ideas and share their dreams with all of us. We need to share their wonderful ideas and
        let them go far and wide to help the human kind get the best of these super leaders. We need to cut the clutter and provide them equitable opportunity
        and a promising platform for help, support and visibility.

Every week, promising Start up Leaders will share their thoughts, work, learnings and future plans on the platform of Prabisha Startup Network. Join us in this
        mission to help our thought leaders achieve their full potential.
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_activity">navigation_activity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>


</resources>