<resources>
    <string name="app_name"><b>Prabisha Startup Network</b></string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_activity">navigation_activity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="about_us_detail_first">They think and explore new ways to make our day to day life
        easier and better by implementing their billion dollar ideas on the ground.

Their ideas have the potential to change our world forever. Today, there are many examples
        like Oyo, Paytm, Google, Facebook, HP, Apple, Uber, Tesla, Yulu, etc. who started their journey as a
        startup and have changed our world forever from their unique offerings.

There are many more startup leaders who also have similar big ideas and are daring to change this world but
        COVID19 has impacted their life and work badly. These thought leaders need our help now much more than ever before.
    </string>
    <string name="about_us_detail_second">
        Prabisha Consulting, a trusted name in the area of Digital Marketing, Graphics
        Design and Technology Development is launching an initiative to help such start up leaders express their big
        ideas and share their dreams with all of us. We need to share their wonderful ideas and let them go far and wide
        to help the human kind get the best of these super leaders. We need to cut the clutter and provide them equitable opportunity
        and a promising platform for help, support and visibility.

Every week, promising Start up Leaders will share their thoughts, work, learnings and future plans on the platform of
        Prabisha Startup Network. Join us in this mission to help our thought leaders achieve their full potential.
    </string>
    <string name="PlanningOfStartup">How we are planning to create a startup ecosystem?</string>
    <string name="PSNMembership">PSN Membership</string>
    <string name="feed_information">Every week, promising Startup leaders will share their thoughts, work, learnings and future
        plans on our platform. This would
        be further amplified by PSN team on a number of online and offline platforms for greater visibility.</string>
    <string name="Home_heading">Who are startup leaders?</string>
    <string name="Home_information">Start Up leaders are real change makers of our times.
        They dare to dream.
        They think and explore new ways to make our day to day life easier and better by implementing their billion dollar ideas on the ground.
Their ideas have the potential to change our world forever. Today, there are many examples like Oyo,
        Paytm, Google, Facebook, HP, Apple, Uber, Tesla, Yulu, etc. who started their journey as a startup and have changed our world
        forever from their unique offerings.
There are many more startup leaders who also have similar big ideas and are daring to change this world but COVID19 has impacted their life and work badly.
        These thought leaders need our help now much more than ever before.</string>
    <string name="Who_we_are">Prabisha Startup Network is an initiative started by Prabisha Consulting,
        a trusted name in the area of Digital Marketing,Graphic Design and Technology Development.</string>
    <string name="Services_Branding_marketing">Branding and Marketing</string>
    <string name="Services_Website_Development">Website Design and Development</string>
    <string name="Services_Digital_Marketing">Digital Marketing</string>
    <string name="Services_Video_Animation_Prod">Video and Animation Production</string>
    <string name="Services_Company_Registration">Company Registration</string>
    <string name="Services_Hiring_Support">Hiring Support</string>
    <string name="Services_Website_Developmen_details"></string>
    <string name="Services_Digital_Marketing_deatils"></string>
    <string name="Services_Video_Animation_Prod_deatils"></string>
    <string name="Services_Branding_marketing_deatils"></string>
    <string name="news_1">IRCTC net profit declines 62% to Rs 78 crore in December quarter</string>
    <string name="news_2">LIVE: UP govt asks police officers to end farmers protests in state</string>
    <string name="news_3">CybSafe raises $7.9M Series A led by IQ Capital for its ‘behavioral’ cybersecurity platform</string>
    <string name="news_4">Smartphone sales slowed decline in Q4, with a big assist from Apple</string>
    <string name="news_5">TIME TO GET OFF THE SIDELINES AND GET IN THE GAME</string>
    <string name="news_6">THIS IS MY STORY: HOW I FOUND MY PURPOSE AND TURNED MY IDEAS INTO A MULTI-MILLION DOLLAR BUSINESS</string>
    <string name="news_7">Online education firm LawSikho signs pact with MEPSC for law courses</string>
    <string name="news_8">Education companies revenues to remain flat in 2020-21: Report</string>
    <string name="news_9">Expecting a rebound in health services soon, says Ayushman Bharat CEO</string>
    <string name="news_10">Adani Ports raises $500 mn selling 10-year bonds to foreign investors</string>
    <string name="blog1">1. How Indian Start-ups are helping in nation Building</string>
    <string name="blog1_detail">India is remarkably growing and developing among various sectors of the Industry such as FINTECH,
        AI (artificial intelligence), MedTech, hospitality, automobiles, and more. Here, start-ups play a significant role. Start-ups
        are small companies with fewer funds and few entrepreneurs, But despite being a small company it has an immense
        role to play in economic growth and development. They also help in contributing to innovation and injecting competition.
        Allowing the start-ups to bring a ray of hope to the people that lack capital shouldn’t be the restrictive factor.

        An idea, no matter how small can be the new big innovation out there. Today, the building
        of a nation depends on the quality and scale of start-ups that any country possesses. In India,
        there is a rise in the number of start-ups from the previous year. India has become a hub of creativity where
        people are keen to learn, explore, and are hardworking which results in pushing up several new start-ups. There was an
        addition of about more than 1300 start-ups from distinct sectors in 2019. These start-ups allow entrepreneurs to show
        their creativity and also provide them with the platform for the same. Due to these start-ups, there is a great jump
        in employment. Every new start-up needs a team, workers, staff to work along with.

        Around 500 million users of the Internet are from rural areas and the smaller town of India.
        Start-ups have also resulted in removing the gap between urban and rural areas, instead, they
        also allow them to learn and showcase their talent in front of the whole society. Start-ups have become
        the resource for the people who have talent but due to lack of money and technology they are not able to
        accomplish their dreams. Many successful start-ups have shown tremendous results in very little time such
        as One97 (Paytm) industry, Ola cabs, Snapdeal, Swiggy, Zomato, and many more. The Government of India has
        also supported our youth with their projects and has taken adequate steps to promote the culture of entrepreneurship in the country.

        Start-up India initiative (or start-up India program) was launched by the Indian Government in 2016 for supporting
        entrepreneurs by building a robust start-up ecosystem, giving them funding support and the government also started
        ‘GeM Start-up Runway’ is a special concept launched by GeM (Government e-marketplace) in partnership with Start-up India.
        The platform grants an opportunity for start-ups where they can directly get orders from government buyers. Under the Start-up
        India program, the government also created the ‘Fund of funds of start-ups(FFS) with a collection of INR 10,000 crore funding promising start-ups.

        We have already witnessed a lot of successful businesses that started as mere start-ups and a lot more are yet to come.
        Start-up indeed is the seeds that help to grow a more powerful and technically strong nation. India is on the path to build
        a nation that attracts and inspires not only the citizens of our county but also other nations. Start-ups are playing a key
        role in economic growth and they create more jobs which mean more employment and which results in an improved economy.</string>
    <string name="blog2">2. Build your own Cloud Storage System using <b>Nextcloud</b></string>
    <string name="blog2_detail">Why waste valuable storage space on your PC or phone when you can store documents and media in the cloud?
        Computer systems have been steadily moving away from local storage to remote, server based storage and processing – which is also known
        as the cloud.
        Is cloud storage really needed?
        Cloud storage is ideal when you want to access your personal files, documents, videos or images quickly. With the cloud, your data is
        stored on hardware that is in a remote physical location, which can then be accessed from any device over the Internet. Cloud storage
        delivers a cost-effective, scalable alternative to storing files in on-premise hard drives or storage networks.
        If you don’t yet have a service for storing and syncing your data in the cloud, you should seriously consider using one.</string>
    <string name="blog3">3. Build a Backup and Recovery Solution with <b>Duplicati</b></string>
    <string name="blog3_detail">Data volume has been growing exponentially, and dramatically increasing opportunities for theft and accidental disclosure
        of sensitive information as well as sequential data loss. The most important preventive measure against data loss is to back
        up all your data and create recovery mechanisms.
        There can be various situations that might result in loss of data. For example, a computer or hard drive failure could make data irretrievable,
        or even theft of a computer system could lead to loss of information. There is always the possibility of a virus or malware being
        introduced to a computer, which can erase a hard drive or prevent anyone from accessing it. Natural calamities such as fire, flood, or an
        earthquake could lead to computer damage, preventing you from accessing files on your computer.
        Data loss can happen to anyone at any time, and it might happen when we least expect it or are least prepared. So, you need to have your data
        backed up and available. Data backup is the best strategy to recover from accidental or malicious data loss.</string>

    <string name="technology_details">At Intentico, we believe your business is unique and so are your customers. Your needs are different at
        different times and so are the needs of your customers based on innumerable factors. You can rely on our Virtual Assistants being smart
        personal assistants for your customers and augment your human agents, operate 24/7 and provide multiple benefits . With us, you build a
        brand of customer service that is faster, cheaper and better. Give the choice of channel to your customers yet reduce service costs or increase
        revenues by deploying our solutions. Artificial Intelligence : The team brings in top-notch Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Natural Language
        Processing (NLU/NLG) capabilities. Business Experience The team understands live chat, bot, IVR, voice, optimization, campaigns , customer and
        business. Domain Knowledge : Team has rich experience in banking, telecom, retail, e-commerce, healthcare and customer service domains Singular
        Experience : Maintain one unique and singular experience across your customer interaction channels . The 1 minute CX : Showcase a fantastic
        customer experience in 1 minute by deploying our bots on your interaction channels . CX Partners : We understand your challenges and are with
        you till we deliver committed results.
    </string>
    <string name="education_detail_1">Samagraa is an independent, non profit, non government charitable trust. It is a passion project,
        run by enthusiasts for the well being and to bridge the academic and social gap of children coming from economically weak backgrounds
        who have gained admission in premier, mainstream schools of Delhi, under the Right to Education act, in the EWS category. Our mission is
        to empower these kids to strike a balance for a better socio- economic development in their lives. Our Aim is to maximise the benefit these children
        have been given due to the government’s policy of inclusion and help them take a leap in life, by enhancing their skills.</string>
    <string name="education_detail_2">To develop happy, responsible, sensitive, academically oriented, balanced kids .
        To train the children to set themselves clear goals and to encourage and direct them to work towards achieving them.
        To empower the children with the skills of rationalization,
        to enable them to take critical life decisions later. To inspire individual, responsible, creative thinking.</string>
    <string name="healthcare_detail">Wings Within is an organization catering to end-to-end solutions in the area of Emotional Wellness,
        Special Education needs, Life Skills coaching, Psychological Assessments, research and training. Counseling relationships will vary
        according to need but may be concerned with developmental issues, addressing and resolving specific problems, making informed decisions,
        coping with crisis. We offer state-of-the-art psychological assessments to help arrive at logical hypotheses about individuals and their
        behavior, personality, preferences and capabilities. Psychological assessment is also known as psychological testing or battery assessment.
        With Life Skills coaching, we set robust platform to explore abilities for adaptive and positive behavior that enables individuals to deal
        effectively with the demands and challenges of everyday life. We customize our programs to align with counselees or clients requirements
        by providing 1 on 1 (face to face) interaction, email communication, over phone and at work place.</string>
    <string name="social_detail_1">We connect blood donor with blood seeker so that a donor can see visible impact created by their blood in someone’s life .
        Our platform connects blood donors and blood seekers on real time which reduces time. </string>
    <string name="social_detail_2">Samagraa is an independent, non profit, non government charitable trust. It is a passion project, run by enthusiasts for the
        well being and to bridge the academic and social gap of children coming from economically weak backgrounds.</string>
    <string name="women_detail_1">Wings Within is an organization catering to end-to-end solutions in the area of Emotional Wellness, Special Education needs,
        Life Skills coaching, Psychological Assessments, research and training. Counseling relationships will vary according to need but may be concerned
        with developmental issues, addressing and resolving specific problems, making informed decisions, coping with crisis. We offer state-of-the-art
        psychological assessments to help arrive at logical hypotheses about individuals and their behavior, personality, preferences and capabilities.
        Psychological assessment is also known as psychological testing or battery assessment. With Life Skills coaching, we set robust platform
        to explore abilities for adaptive and positive behavior that enables individuals to deal effectively with the demands and challenges of
        everyday life. We customize our programs to align with counselees or clients requirements by providing 1 on 1 (face to face) interaction,
        email communication, over phone and at work place.</string>
    <string name="women_detail_2">Samagraa is an independent, non profit, non government charitable trust. It is a passion project, run by enthusiasts
        for the well being and to bridge the academic and social gap of children coming from economically weak backgrounds who have gained admission in
        premier, mainstream schools of Delhi, under the Right to Education act, in the EWS category. Our mission is to empower these kids to strike a
        balance for a better socio- economic development in their lives. Our Aim is to maximise the benefit
        these children have been given due to the government’s policy of inclusion and help them take a leap in life, by enhancing their skills.</string>
    <string name="our_vision_at_smagara">To develop happy, responsible, sensitive, academically oriented, balanced kids .  To train the children to
        set themselves clear goals and to encourage and direct them to work towards achieving them. To empower the children with the skills of rationalization,
        to enable them to take critical life decisions later. To inspire individual, responsible, creative thinking.</string>
    <string name="faq_ques_1">How do we become a member?</string>
    <string name="faq_ans_1">You can join us through any of the platforms/channels.\n
        www.linkedin.com/company/prabisha \n
        www.facebook.com/prabishastartupnetwork \n
        www.instagram.com/ \n
        www.twitter.com/prabishac
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ques_2">Is there any criteria that you look for before publishing a startup story?
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ans_2">Although our focus areas are technology, education, women empowerment, healthcare,
        rural development and social sector but we wish to encourage all the thought leaders who have dared to bring a change.
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ques_3">What all platforms do you publish your stories on?
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ans_3">Linkedin, Facebook, Twitter, YouTube are some of the social media platforms we are using at pres
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ques_4">What are the various modes in which you conduct the interviews ?
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ans_4">We conduct interviews through online video platforms.
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ques_5">If I come to you with an idea in what all ways will you be able to help me?
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ans_5">We would be able to help you with various.  services like digital marketing, web development, graphic designing at a reasonable cost.
        Not only this but we would be able to provide all other resources through our vast startup network which is growing fast.
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ques_6">What are the benefits of being a part of Prabisha Startup Network?
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ans_6">It would help you reach out to the larger audience.
        It will give you a platform wherein you can share, collaborate and innovate new ideas with other thought leaders.
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ques_7">Do you charge any fee for interviewing or sharing success stories of startups?
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ans_7">No, We do not charge any fees. You only need to get in touch with us to proceed further.
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ques_8">What is the eligibility criteria to join PSN?
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ans_8">Your startup should be 6 months to 5 years old.The offerings can be regular/unique.
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ques_9">Why do Investors invest in Startups?
    </string>
    <string name="faq_ans_9">Investing in startups is a risky proposition, but the low requirement for overhead
        capital combined with high upside potential, makes it lucrative for investors to put their bets on startups.

The Thomson Reuters Venture Capital Research Index replicated the performance of the venture capital industry in
        2012 and found that overall venture capital has returned at an annual
        rate of 20% since 1996 – far outperforming modest returns of 7.5% and 5.9% from public equities and bonds respectively.
    </string>
    <string name="internshp_detail">At PSN, you have the chance to gain deep insights into different areas of work while you are still studying.

Join us for an internship and realize your dreams with us.

Interested students can send their resume to psn@prabisha.com</string>
    <string name="address">Headquarters : D4/4029, Vasant Kunj,New Delhi - 110070 \n \n
         Bangalore : 3051, Prabisha Consulting \n
        Prestige Sunnyside Oak \n
        Sarjapur ORR, Bangalore - 560103</string>
    <string name="social_startup_detail">A social entrepreneur takes initiatives to solve community-based problems. They take on the risk and make
        effort to create positive changes in society through their initiatives. At PSN, we encourage such changemakers and provide all possible support
        to their endeavours. Glad to introduce some of such wonderful changemakers on PSN platform</string>
    
    <string name="website_dev_detail">We design professional websites for your online presence.</string>
    <string name="digital_marketing_detail">Our Digital Marketing services can boost up your lead generation in a short span of time. </string>
    <string name="video_ani_detail">Video and Animation are key to increase your reach today. Do let us know your requirements.</string>
    <string name="servivces_intro">Prabisha is focused on providing customised business solutions to budding and visionary Entrepreneurs and Startup Leaders.
        They provide their services in the areas of 3D’s – Development, Design and Digital Marketing. </string>
    <string name="Learning_and_development">Learning and development is quintessential for any organization. By constantly up-skilling employees,
        companies grow and add more value. It also plays a critical role in employee engagement.

Fast growing start ups need support to help them in L and D and we aim to provide them support by identifying the L and D need and customised solutions
        with help of our partners.</string>
    <string name="carresr_detail">Startups are seeds of a great revolution. If you have ideas, ingenuity and a passion
        for developing something new, making a difference, come and be a part of our team.
We are a diverse team of exceptional people, the latest and promising tech and business companies across industries.
Together, we work to bring meaningful and sustainable change to make this world a better place for everyone.

Come join us to start a new journey. Interested people can send their resume to psn@prabisha.com</string>

</resources>